{
    "subject": "resource/Israel_Zangwill",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/The_Melting_Pot_(play)",
    "human_readable": "Israel Zangwill's notable work is 'The Melting Pot'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8526309728622437,
            "question": "What is the title of Israel Zangwill's notable work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42030227184295654,
            "question": "Who wrote 'The Melting Pot'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37277865409851074,
            "question": "How is the concept of assimilation presented in 'The Melting Pot'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3468324542045593,
            "question": "What theme does 'The Melting Pot' explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34231868386268616,
            "question": "What are some key symbols used in 'The Melting Pot'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3380674123764038,
            "question": "When was 'The Melting Pot' published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3353527784347534,
            "question": "What impact did 'The Melting Pot' have on American culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3190270960330963,
            "question": "What literary genre does 'The Melting Pot' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3084287643432617,
            "question": "What social issues does 'The Melting Pot' address?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30519577860832214,
            "question": "Is 'The Melting Pot' a novel, play, or poem?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Israel Zangwill's notable work is 'The Melting Pot'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8322_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What social issues does 'The Melting Pot' address?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8322_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What literary genre does 'The Melting Pot' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8322_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did 'The Melting Pot' have on American culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8322_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8322_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAll the provided documents mention Israel Zangwill and his play \"The Melting Pot\" as one of his notable works. Therefore, the statement that Israel Zangwill's notable work is 'The Melting Pot' is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer aligns with the information provided in the documents, which confirm that Israel Zangwill wrote \"The Melting Pot,\" a play that was influential and widely recognized."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}